https://www.mmauniverse.com/privacy-statement.html

Welcome to MMA Universe
Welcome to Europe's best-known MMA Store, we've been serving fighters and fans alike since 1998, we have literally thousands of items in stock and ready to ship Worldwide!
View Our Brands
Sale & Clearance Items
Fight Wear
MMA Fight Wear
Choose from a wide range of MMAFight Wear and Casual Wear,from the brands you love at aprice that won't be beat!
MMA Shorts
MMA T-Shirts
MMA Hoodies
Rash Guards
BJJ GI
MMA Headwear
Accessories
Fight Gear
MMA Fight Gear
All the essentials for everyMMA Athlete from battle testedbrands at unbeatable prices!
MMA Gloves
Shin & Knee Pads
Boxing Gloves
Mouth Guards
Compression Gear
Groin Protection
Hand Wraps
Instructional Books
Gear Bags
MMA on DVD
MMA on DVD
Own a part of MMA History,with Events from aroundthe world on DVD!
Instructional DVD Sets
MMA Multi Packs
Japanese MMA& Kickboxing
British MMA Events
North American MMA
BJJ & Grappling
Categories
Fight Wear
MMA Universe Help Center - Privacy Statement
We at MMAUniverse.com know that you care about how information about you is used and we appreciate your trust in us to do this carefully and sensibly. This page describes the privacy policy of MMAUniverse.com. By visiting MMAUniverse.com, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
Legal owner of MMA Universe
The legal entity in control of MMA Universe is Martialartshop Limited. MMA universe is a trading name of Martialartshop Limited who operate from within the United Kingdom
What personal information does MMAUniverse.com gather about customers?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalise and improve your shopping experience at MMAUniverse.com. We use the information to handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers, update our records, display content such as customer reviews and recently viewed items and generally maintain your accounts with us. We also use this information to improve our store and prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website.
These are the following types of information that we gather:
Information You Give Us: If you register an account with us, we will store any information you provide for your future use. We use the information that you provide within orders you place and any communication between yourself and our staff.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. This information is not personally identifyable and is used to allow us to improve your shopping experience with us.
E-mail Communications: From time to time MMA Universe sends email newsletters. When you register your account is included in our mailing list however it is possible to unsubscribe at any time via your account control panel on this website.
What about Cookies?
Cookies are unique identifiers that we transfer to your device to enable our systems to recognise your device and to provide features that improve your shopping experience. We do not store any personally identifiable information in any cookies.
Does MMA Universe share information with any third parties?
Absolutely not. MMA Universe will not disclose, sell or share any of your personal information with any company, organisation or person outside of MMA Universe and it's parent company, Martialartshop Limited. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties. We consider all information supplied by you to be highly confidential and will ensure that the information supplied by you is handled in a strictly confidential manner at all times. MMA Universe takes all possible steps so ensure that our company complies with the regulations of the UK Data Protection Act 1998.
Exclusions:
Any third party website that is linked from this website is not bound by this privacy statement and is instead bound by the privacy statement of that particular website.
How MMA Universe protects it's customers
MMAUniverse.com uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to provide you with the safe and secure shopping experience. SSL technology enables encryption (scrambling) of sensitive information, including passwords and credit card numbers, during your online transactions.
All of the sensitive forms on our site are secured with SSL technology so your personal information stays safe and out of malicious hands. In addition, our SSL Certificate is provided by GeoTrust and we are certified Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) Compliant, our website is tested regularly by Security Metrics.
Conditions of use, notices, and revisions
If you have any concern about privacy at MMAUniverse.com, please get in touch us with a thorough description and we will try to resolve the issue for you. Our business changes fequently and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use and Sale may change as a result.
Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make however and will never change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past.
Contacting Us
Martialartshop Limited (trading as MMA Universe) is the data controller for the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998.
You have the right to access the information which MMA Universe holds about you and your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £15.00 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. We are always more than happy to hear from our customers (even in the case of complaints!). We are always grateful for any time you spend providing us with the knowledge we need to ensure our customers are completely satisfied - we want you to return to the site and to recommend us to your friends and family.
If you have any questions, comments or feedback about our privacy policy, or if you would like us to stop processing your information, please do not hesitate to contact customer services, who will be delighted to answer any questions you may have.
Your Name:Your Email:
Find Us:
© 2005 - 2020 MMA Universe. All Rights ReservedMMA Universe is a trading name of Martialartshop Limited.
Privacy Statement | Copyright Information | Terms of Use
We Accept:
